Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES IV. Subject Files, 1928-1980
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES IV. SUBJECT FILES
  - Grants, Policies and Procedures, Dept. HEW Guidelines
    - 1971-74 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - 1975-79 (Box 117)
  - Grants for Family Planning Projects, Policies and Procedures 1968-72 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Grants, Policies and Procedures (Box 117)
    - FP Grants For Affiliates: Points to Consider Before Applying for Fed. Funds, undated (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Program Guidelines for Family Planning Services, Section 1001 Public Health Services Act, January 1975-76 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Grants: Grants and Contracts 1971-72Administrative Charges (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Grants from PPWP
    - 1973-74 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - 1975-79 (Box 117)
    - 1970-73 (Box 117, Folder 10-12)
  - Grants to PPWP
    - Restricted Grants and Contracts Received 1974, 1975 & 1976 (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - 1975-79 (Box 117, Folder 14-16)
    - 1973-74 (Box 117, Folder 17-18)
    - 1972-74 (Box 117, Folder 19)
    - 1975-76 (Box 117)
    - 1971 (Box 117, Folder 20)
    - Family Planning Services Project Grant List, NCFPS, Dept. HEW 1972 (Box 117, Folder 21)
    - OEO Family Planning Projects, As of July 1971 (Box 117, Folder 22)
    - 1966-71 (Box 117, Folder 23-27)
    - Government Grants 1966-70 (Box 117, Folder 28)
    - HEW Grants to Planned Parenthood Affiliates 1969-71 (Box 117, Folder 29)
    - The Worcester Foundation, The Pill 1959 (Box 117, Folder 30)
    - Public Welfare Foundation Grant, Intrauterine Devices 1965-66 (Box 117, Folder 31)
  - Grants, Restricted Grants 1969-72 (Box 117, Folder 32)
  - Naomi Gray Associates, Inc.
    - 1970-74 (Box 117, Folder 33)
    - 1975 (Box 117)
    - Workshops on Family Life Education and Family Planning for the Mentally Retarded 1973-74 (Box 117, Folder 34)
  - Gu, Misc. 1958-67 (Box 117, Folder 35)
  - Alan F. Guttmacher, Biographical Material
    - Alan F. Guttmacher [Biographical] 1966-73 (Box 117, Folder 36)
    - Staff, Guttmacher, Alan F., Biographical Material 1962-74 (Box 117, Folder 37)
    - Staff, Dr. Alan F. Guttmacher, Awards 1967-74 (Box 117, Folder 38)
    - Administration, Guttmacher, A. F., Autobiography, Rough Draft 1972 (Box 117, Folder 39)
    - Guttmacher, Alan F., MD, Honorial Program Mt. Sinai School of Medicine, 75th Birthday, May 19, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 40)
    - Dr. Guttmacher's Testimonial Banquet, Baltimore, Maryland, November 14, 1967 (Box 117, Folder 41)
    - Staff, Guttmacher, Dr. A.F., Obituary 1974 (Box 117, Folder 42)
    - Staff, Dr. A. F. Guttmacher
      - Abortion 1969-72 (Box 117, Folder 43)
      - Correspondence 1965-66, 1969-74 (Box 117, Folder 44-45)
      - The Commission on Population Growth and the American Future 1972 (Box 117, Folder 46)
      - Consultation and Advice 1969-70 (Box 117, Folder 47)
      - Dept. of Defense 1968-69 (Box 117, Folder 48)
      - Department of H.E.W. 1971-73 (Box 117, Folder 49)
      - Department of State, A.I.D. 1970 (Box 117, Folder 50)
      - The Environment, Correspondence 1969 (Temporary Folder) (Box 117, Folder 51)
      - Ford Foundation, Correspondence 1962 (Box 117, Folder 52)
      - HSMHA, Protest Re: Proposed Rules, 42 CFR Part 50 1973 (Box 118, Folder 1)
      - Remarks, First Day of Issue, Family Planning Stamp, March 17, 1972 (Box 118, Folder 2)
      - Memos 1970-72 (Box 118, Folder 3)
      - Minority Relations 1969 (Temporary File) (Box 118, Folder 4)
      - McCormick Bequest Fund 1968-70 (Box 118, Folder 5)
      - Nelson Hearings, Source of Material for A.F.G. Testimony 1966-70 (Box 118, Folder 6)
      - Nelson Hearings
        - A.F.G. Testimony 1970 (Box 118, Folder 7)
        - Mimeos, General 1970 (Box 118, Folder 8)
        - Impact of Nelson Hearings 1970 (Box 118, Folder 9)
        - Correspondence 1970 (Box 118, Folder 10)
        - Press Releases 1970 (Box 118, Folder 11)
      - Report of Travels to India 1971 (Box 118, Folder 12)
      - Representations To Government Officials 1971 (Box 118, Folder 13)
      - Speeches 1966-70 (Box 118, Folder 14)
      - T.V.
        - Mike Douglas Show 1970 (Box 118, Folder 15)
        - The Today Show 1970 (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - T.V. Correspondence
      - Buckley, Guttmacher Show 1969-70 (Box 118, Folder 17)
      - David Frost Show, Guttmacher 1969-70 (Box 118, Folder 18)
    - Staff, Guttmacher, Dr. A.F., Tydings Bill S 2108 1969 (Box 118, Folder 19)
    - Outcard for Guttmacher, Dr. A.F., President's Letter and Confidential Material (Box 118, Folder 20)
  - H, Misc. 1961-69 (Box 118, Folder 21)
  - Hall, Dr. Robert E. 1956-69 (Box 118, Folder 22)
  - Han, Misc. 1960-61 (Box 118, Folder 23)
  - Har, Misc. 1962-69 (Box 118, Folder 24)
  - Hardin, Garrett 1965-69 (Box 118, Folder 25)
  - Hartman, Dr. Carl G. 1956-68 (Box 118, Folder 26)
  - Has, Misc. 1963-69 (Box 118, Folder 27)
  - Hauser, Prof. Philip M. 1956-60 (Box 118, Folder 28)
  - He, Misc.
    - 1962-74 (Box 118, Folder 29)
    - 1975-79 (Box 118)
  - Health Insurance Plan of Greater N.Y.
    - 1955-74 (Box 118, Folder 30)
    - 1975-79 (Box 118)
  - HMOs (Health Maintenance Organizations) 1975 (Box 118, Folder 31)
  - Heller, Carl M.D. 1962, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 32)
  - Hellman, Dr. Louis 1955-67 (Box 118, Folder 33)
  - Hen, Misc. 1955-65 (Box 118, Folder 34)
  - Her, Misc. 1957-67 (Box 118, Folder 35)
  - Herz, Mr. and Mrs. Herbert 1958-61 (Box 118, Folder 36)
  - Hi, Misc.
    - 1962-74 (Box 118, Folder 37)
    - 1975-79 (Box 118)
  - Ho, Misc.
    - 1963-74 (Box 118, Folder 38)
    - 1975-79 (Box 118)
  - Hoffman, Jean Lazarus from 1980 (Box 118, Folder 39)
  - Holland Rantos Company, Inc. 1975-79 (Box 118, Folder 40)
  - Hon, Misc. 1965-68 (Box 118, Folder 41)
  - Hospitals
    - Directory, Questionnaire, Correspondence 1957-67 (Box 118, Folder 42)
    - General 1955-69 (Box 118, Folder 43)
    - Hill-Burton Act 1955-62 (Box 118, Folder 44)
  - Houghton Mifflin Co. 1964-67 (Box 118, Folder 45)
  - Hu, Misc. 1956-69 (Box 118, Folder 46)
  - Huxley, Aldous 1957-63 (Box 118, Folder 47)
  - Huxley-Canfield Statement
    - Correspondence 1960-68 (Box 118, Folder 48-49)
    - Huxley, Julian 1955-62 (Box 118, Folder 50)
    - General 1960-61 (Box 118, Folder 51)
    - Signers, June-Nov. 1960, undated (Box 118, Folder 52)
  - I, Misc. 1963-69 (Box 118, Folder 53)
  - Illegitimacy 1958-71 (Box 118, Folder 54)
  - Infertility 1954-69 (Box 118, Folder 55)
  - International Business Machines Corporation, Correspondence
    - 1966-74 (Box 118, Folder 56)
    - 1975-77 (Box 118)
  - International, General 1955-70 (Box 118, Folder 57)
  - International Women's Year
    - 1974-75 (Box 118, Folder 58)
    - Bulletin 1975 (Box 118, Folder 59)
  - International Year of the Child 1976-79 (Box 118, Folder 60)
  - In Vitro Fertilization 1978-79 (Box 118, Folder 61)
  - J, Misc.
    - 1954-74 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - 1975-79 (Box 119)
  - Jacobi, Dr. Abraham 1912 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Jaffe, Fred
    - Printed material 1977-78 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence and Memos 1964-69 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Estimated Fertility By Poverty Status, 1966-70, and Changes, 1971 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Exploration Means of Including PPWP Hdqtr.'s Costs in Affiliate Govt. Grants 1972 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Local Area Study of Abortion (LASA), 1974 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Memo on the Objectives of PPWP, Individual and Societal 1971 (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - 1970 National Fertility Survey Notes, 1971 (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Questions and Answers Concerning the Center 1971 (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - Report on the Center's Fund Raising 1974 (Box 119, Folder 11)
    - Report on the Accomplishments of the Center 1968-71 (Box 119, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence and Memos 1970-74 (Box 119, Folder 13)
    - Articles, Papers, Speeches
      - Articles 1977 (Box 119, Folder 14)
      - Data Gaps in Planning for Comprehensive Fertility-Related Health Services, Jaffe, F.S. and Muller, C. 1972 (Box 119, Folder 15)
      - Family Planning and Public Policy: Who is Misleading Whom?, Harkavy, Jaffe, and Wishik 1969 (Box 119, Folder 16)
      - Health Policy and Population Policy: A Relationship Redefined, APHA 1972 (Box 119, Folder 17)
      - Planned Parenthood's Identity Crisis and the Imperative for Change, N.E. Regional Conference 1967 (Box 119, Folder 18)
      - Fertility Control Policy, Social Policy and Population Policy 1974 (Box 119, Folder 19)
      - Man's Relationship to the Environment as Influenced by Overpopulation 1969 (Box 119, Folder 20)
      - Modernizing U.S. Fertility Behavior: Current Status and Options 1974 (Box 119, Folder 21)
      - Negro Fertility and Family Size Preferences: Implications for Programming of Health and Social Services 1966 (Box 119, Folder 22)
      - Special Summary: Paper on National Fertility Study 1970 (Box 119, Folder 23)
      - Towards The Reduction of Unwanted Pregnancy: Frederick S. Jaffe (Box 119, Folder 24)
      - Hormonal Contraceptives in Fertility Control Programs, Jaffe 1977 (Box 119, Folder 25)
    - Alan Guttmacher Institute, Appointment as President 1977 (Box 119, Folder 26)
    - Obituary 1978 (Box 119, Folder 27)
  - Jo, Misc. (Box 119, Folder 28)
    - 1962-74 (Box 119)
    - 1975-79 (Box 119)
  - Juvenile Delinquency, Correspondence 1955-68 (Box 119, Folder 29)
  - K, Misc.
    - 1965-74 (Box 119, Folder 30)
    - 1975-79 (Box 119)
  - Ke, Misc. 1962-73 (Box 119, Folder 31)
  - Keller, Vaughn, Consultant from 1979 (Box 119, Folder 32)
  - Ki, Misc. 1958-69 (Box 119, Folder 33)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King, Mrs. Martin Luther King 1968-70 (Box 119, Folder 34)
  - Kl, Misc.
    - 1956-74 (Box 119, Folder 35)
    - 1975-77 (Box 119)
  - Knopf, Alfred A. 1955-66 (Box 119, Folder 36)
  - Kr, Misc. 1963-66 (Box 119, Folder 37)
  - L, Misc.
    - 1964-74 (Box 119, Folder 38)
    - 1975-78 (Box 119)
  - Lader, Lawrence
    - 1955-74 (Box 119, Folder 39)
    - 1975-78 (Box 119)
  - Laidlaw, Dr. Robert 1955-64 (Box 119, Folder 40)
  - Lar, Misc. 1961-69 (Box 119, Folder 41)
  - Lara-Brand, Jorge 1969-70 (Box 119, Folder 42)
  - Lasker, Mrs. Mary 1955-68 (Box 119, Folder 43)
  - Law, Professor Sylvia, New York University School of Law 1978-79 (Box 119, Folder 44)
  - Le, Misc.
    - 1964-74 (Box 119, Folder 45)
    - 1975-79 (Box 119)
  - Len, Misc.
    - 1969-74 (Box 119, Folder 46)
    - 1975-79 (Box 119)
  - Li, Misc. 1959-70 (Box 119, Folder 47)
  - Lincoln Lettershop 1962-67 (Box 119, Folder 48)
  - Lindsay, George N., Correspondence 1966-68 (Box 119, Folder 49)
  - Lo, Misc.
    - 1961-74 (Box 119, Folder 50)
    - 1975-78 (Box 119)
  - Lobsenz and Company, Inc. 1962-64 (Box 119, Folder 51)
  - M, Misc.
    - 1958-74 (Box 119, Folder 52)
    - 1975-79 (Box 119)
  - MacMillan Company 1955-69 (Box 119, Folder 53)
  - Mahoney, Mrs. Florence 1961-65 (Box 119, Folder 54)
  - Mali, Mrs. Henry J., Kay 1961-67 (Box 119, Folder 55)
  - Map, Misc.
    - 1964-74 (Box 119, Folder 56)
    - 1975-79 (Box 119)
  - Maremont, Arnold
    - General Correspondence 1963-68 (Box 119, Folder 57)
    - Project and Misc. Material 1965-68 (Box 119, Folder 58)
  - Marriage Counseling, General 1955-59 (Box 119, Folder 59)
  - Mr. and Mrs. W. L. Martin 1957-63 (Box 119, Folder 60)
  - McA, Misc. 1964-69 (Box 119, Folder 61)
  - McD, Misc. 1959-68 (Box 119, Folder 62)
  - McGraw-Hill (Publishers) 1955-70 (Box 119, Folder 63)
  - McH, Misc. 1962-68 (Box 119, Folder 64)
  - McHugh, Dr. Gelolo
    - 1955-65 (Box 119, Folder 65)
    - Guttmacher, Gould Booklet, Mailings 1959 (Box 119, Folder 66)
  - McIntyre, Henry L. 1970 (Box 119, Folder 67)
  - McKinnon, Edna R. 1960-69 (Box 119, Folder 68)
  - McMaster, Mrs. Philip D. (Eliz) 1954-61 (Box 119, Folder 69)
  - McN, Misc. 1969 (Box 119, Folder 70)
  - Me, Misc.
    - 1964-74 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - 1975-78 (Box 120)
  - Mead Johnson Laboratories, Correspondence 1962-71 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Medicaid, Title XIX
    - 1966-74 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - 1975-79 (Box 120)
  - Meier, Mrs. Gitta 1960-69 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Mental Health
    - 1964-74 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - 1975 (Box 120)
    - Publication Project 1969-72 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Merck Sharp and Dohme 1961-69 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Meyer, Mrs. Eugene (Agnes), Speeches 1956-61 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Microfilm Law and Retention Schedules 1965-66 (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Microfilm Project 1977 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Mi, Misc. 1961-69 (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Migrants, General 1955-64 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Migrant Program, Bob Browning 1969 (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - East Coast, Migrant Project 1965-67 (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - Mills, Mrs. Dudley H. 1955-62 (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - Mills, Mrs. James Paul 1957-69 (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - Mills, Leslie 1955-62 (Box 120, Folder 17)
  - Minority Groups 1947-68 (Box 120, Folder 18)
  - Mo, Misc. 1962-69 (Box 120, Folder 19)
  - Model Cities 1968-70 (Box 120, Folder 20)
  - Montagu, Dr. M.F. Ashley, Correspondence 1957-64 (Box 120, Folder 21)
  - Mott, Stewart 1966-74 (Box 120, Folder 22)
  - Mu, Misc.
    - 1963-74 (Box 120, Folder 23)
    - 1975-78 (Box 120)
  - Mudd, Dr. Stuart 1962-67 (Box 120, Folder 24)
  - Munn, Ector O., Correspondence 1963-70 (Box 120, Folder 25)
  - N, Misc. 1962-68 (Box 120, Folder 26)
  - National Abortion Council 1977-79 (Box 120, Folder 27)
  - National Abortion Federation 1977-79 (Box 120, Folder 28)
  - NARAL, National Abortion Rights Action League
    - 1970-74 (Box 120, Folder 29)
    - 1975-79 (Box 120)
  - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development, Inc., Correspondence 1962-71 (Box 120, Folder 30)
  - National Academy of Sciences 1957-70 (Box 120, Folder 31)
  - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development, Inc., General 1955-67 (Box 120, Folder 32)
  - NAACP, Correspondence, Misc. 1962-68 (Box 120, Folder 33)
  - National Association for Mental Health, Correspondence 1955-68 (Box 120, Folder 34)
  - National Association of Abortion Facilities 1976-77 (Box 120, Folder 35)
  - National Association of Manufacturers 1955-58 (Box 120, Folder 36)
  - National Association of Science Writers 1959-69 (Box 120, Folder 37)
  - National Association of Social Workers, Correspondence 1955-70 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - National Better Business Bureau 1962-68 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - National Coalition of Black Trade Unionists 1977 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - National Commission on Confidentiality of Health Records 1975-79 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - National Committee on Maternal Health, Correspondence 1955-68 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - National Conference, Social Welfare
    - 104th Annual Forum, Chicago, Illinois
      - Correspondence 1976-77 (Box 121, Folder 6)
      - General, Programs, etc. 1977 (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - 102nd Annual Forum, San Francisco, Cal.
      - Correspondence
        - 1974 (Box 121, Folder 8)
        - 1975 (Box 121)
      - General, Programs, etc. 1973-75 (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - 101st Annual Forum, Cincinnati, Ohio 1973-74 (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - National Conference on Social Welfare
    - Annual Forum, Chicago, Ill., General 1972 (Box 121, Folder 11)
    - 1970 Annual Forum, Chicago, Illinois, 1969 (Box 121, Folder 12)
    - 97th Annual Forum, Chicago, Illinois, General, Correspondence 1970 (Box 121, Folder 13)
    - New York, New York, Correspondence 1968-69 (Box 121, Folder 14)
    - New York 1969 (Box 121, Folder 15)
    - San Francisco, Cal.
      - Correspondence, May 26,1967-68 (Box 121, Folder 16)
      - General, Programs, etc. 1968 (Box 121, Folder 17)
    - Dallas, Texas
      - Correspondence 1966-67 (Box 121, Folder 18)
      - General, Programs 1967 (Box 121, Folder 19)
    - 93rd Annual Meeting, Chicago, Ill.
      - General Correspondence 1965-66 (Box 121, Folder 20)
      - General 1965-67 (Box 121, Folder 21)
    - Atlantic City, General Correspondence 1964-65 (Box 121, Folder 22)
    - Los Angeles, General Correspondence 1963-64 (Box 121, Folder 23)
    - Atlantic City, General 1965, May 1965 (Box 121, Folder 24)
    - Los Angeles, General 1963-66 (Box 121, Folder 25)
    - Cleveland
      - Correspondence 1962-73 (Box 121, Folder 26)
      - General 1956-63 (Box 121, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence Meeting 1961-62 (Box 121, Folder 28)
    - 1962 (Box 121, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence 1960-61 (Box 121, Folder 30)
    - General 1961-63 (Box 121, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence 1955-60 (Box 121, Folder 32)
    - Deans' Breakfast 1960 (Box 121, Folder 33)
    - General 1959-61 (Box 121, Folder 34-35)
    - General Correspondence
      - 1965-74 (Box 122, Folder 1)
      - 1975-78 (Box 122)
  - National Council of Churches of Christ in USA, Correspondence
    - 1961-74 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - 1975-78 (Box 122)
    - 1955-60 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - North American Conference, Church and Family 1960-61 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - General 1956-67 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - National Council on Family Relations, Correspondence 1955-68 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - National Council on Illegitimacy 1966-71 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - National Council of Jewish Women 1953-69 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - National Council of Negro Women 1953-69 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - National Council of Women 1957-69 (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - National Convocation on the Challenge of Building Peace, New York City 1968-69 (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - National Development Council
    - Arnold Maremont: Chairman 1967-68 (Box 122, Folder 12)
    - Success Stories 1968 (Box 122, Folder 13)
  - National Family Planning Forum
    - 1971-74 (Box 122, Folder 14)
    - 1975-77 (Box 122)
  - National Federation of Settlements and Neighborhood Centers, Correspondence 1967-68 (Box 122, Folder 15)
  - National Genetics Disease Act 1978 (Box 122, Folder 16)
  - National Groups, Correspondence
    - 1955-74 (Box 122, Folder 17)
    - 1975-78 (Box 122)
  - National Health Council
    - National Health Forum, Correspondence 1955-66 (Box 122, Folder 18)
    - Continuing Education
      - 1965-68 (Box 122, Folder 19)
      - Lists, Events, Misc. 1965-68 (Box 122, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence
      - 1970-74 (Box 122, Folder 21)
      - 1975-76 (Box 122)
      - 1960-69 (Box 122, Folder 22-23)
    - Delegates 1961-69 (Box 122, Folder 24)
    - Directory of Member Organizations, etc. 1956, 1960 (Box 122, Folder 25)
    - Lists, Events, General 1969-71 (Box 122, Folder 26)
    - Members, Lists 1967 (Box 122, Folder 27)
    - Community Health Week 1956-66 (Box 122, Folder 28)
    - National Health Council on the Aging, Correspondence 1962-65 (Box 122, Folder 29)
    - National Health Council, Rockefeller Foundation Exploration, Voluntary Health Agencies 1959-60 (Box 122, Folder 30)
    - Guide for Uniform Accounting and Financial Reporting, January 1967 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Accounting Procedures and Mechanization Feasibility, June 1965 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Layout of Proposed New Location, December 1965 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Publications Distribution Operation, August 1965 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - National Health Council, Uniform Accounting Principles
      - Correspondence 1956-65 (Box 123, Folder 5)
      - General 1956-66 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - National Health Insurance
    - 1971-74 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - 1975-78 (Box 123)
  - National Information Bureau 1970-71 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - National Labor Relations 1974 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - National Information Bureau 1955-70 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - National League for Nursing
    - 1955-74 (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - 1975-78 (Box 123)
  - National Medical Association 1956-69 (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - National Music Publishers Association, Inc. 1979 (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - N.O.N. (National Organization for Non-Parents) 1978-79 (Box 123, Folder 14)
  - NOW (National Organization of Women)
    - 1967-74 (Box 123, Folder 15)
    - 1975-78 (Box 123)
  - National Public Relations Council, Correspondence 1955-69 (Box 123, Folder 16)
  - National Social Welfare Assembly 1964-67 (Box 123, Folder 17)
  - National Tuberculosis Association 1963-69 (Box 123, Folder 18)
  - National Urban League
    - Correspondence 1962-74 (Box 123, Folder 19-20)
    - Misc. and Field Trips 1956-68 (Box 123, Folder 21)
  - National Women's Health Coalition 1973 (Box 123, Folder 22)
  - Ne, Misc.
    - 1964-74 (Box 123, Folder 23)
    - 1975-77 (Box 123)
  - Negative Population Growth, Inc. 1977 (Box 123, Folder 24)
  - Negro Attitudes (All Transferred to "Black Attitudes") from 1962 (empty) (Box 123, Folder 25)
  - Negro Problem, Correspondence 1962-68 (Box 123, Folder 26)
  - NEW 1963-69 (Box 123, Folder 27)
  - New Jersey Bell 1978-79 (Box 123, Folder 28)
  - New York Academy of Medicine 1931-46 (Box 123, Folder 29)
  - New York Civil Liberties Union 1978 (Box 123, Folder 30)
  - New York Health Show
    - General 1958-61 (Box 123, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence 1958-61 (Box 123, Folder 32)
  - New York Public Library 1955-63 (Box 123, Folder 33)
  - New York State Campaign for Abortion Rights 1978-79 (Box 123, Folder 34)
  - New Yorkers for Abortion Law Repeal 1972 (Box 123, Folder 35)
  - Newspapers
    - Clippings, New York Times 1955-68 (Box 123, Folder 36)
    - General Correspondence 1955-71 (Box 123, Folder 37)
    - Report on New York Times Ad for Winfield Best, circa late 1960s (Box 123, Folder 38)
    - Associated Press, Correspondence 1958-69 (Box 123, Folder 39)
    - N.Y. Herald Tribune, Correspondence 1955-66 (Box 123, Folder 40)
    - New York Times, Correspondence 1964-70 (Box 123, Folder 41)
    - New York Post, Correspondence 1957-69 (Box 123, Folder 42)
    - New York Times, Correspondence 1955-72 (Box 123, Folder 43)
    - NY World Tel & Sun, Correspondence 1955-65 (Box 123, Folder 44)
    - Pulitzer Committee 1959 (Box 123, Folder 45)
    - United Press Association, Correspondence 1955-69 (Box 123, Folder 46)
    - Wall Street Journal 1965-69 (Box 123, Folder 47)
  - No, Misc. 1964-72 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Nobel Laureates
    - Statement 1960-61 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Pope Pius, Correspondence 1965-69 (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Statement 1962 (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Petition the Pope, Reprint: New York Times 1965 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Statement 1962-63 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Nuveen, Mr. John 1955-68 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Nurses Manual Folder 1955-60 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - O, Misc. 1967-69 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - On, Misc. 1953-69 (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Oram, Harold 1959-69 (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Ortho Pharmaceutical Corp.
    - Correspondence
      - 1958-74 (Box 124, Folder 12-14)
  - Osborn, Robert 1955-65 (Box 124, Folder 15)
  - Organization of American States
    - 1964-68 (Box 124, Folder 16)
    - Spanish and English, Speeches, Washington, DC 1964-65 (Box 124, Folder 17)
    - Speeches, Washington, DC 1964 (Box 124, Folder 18)
  - Organon, Diagnostics 1975-77 (Box 124, Folder 19)
  - Osborn, Fairfield 1949-63 (Box 124, Folder 20)
  - P, Misc. 1964-69 (Box 124, Folder 21)
  - Pa, Misc. 1978 (Box 124, Folder 22)
  - Papanicolaou Smears
    - Automated Medical Services of Ohio, Inc., Newspapers, Publicity, Miscellaneous 1978 (Box 124, Folder 23)
    - Cytology Screening Laboratory
      - 1970-74 (Box 124, Folder 24)
      - 1975-78 (Box 124)
    - Automated Medical Services of Ohio, Inc.
      - 1978 (Box 124, Folder 25)
      - PP Affiliates Recall 1978 (Box 124, Folder 26)
    - Cytology Laboratories (Used by PP - by Region) 1978 (Box 124, Folder 27)
    - Cancer Screening Services (CSS) 1970 (Formerly Cancer Control Center)
      - 1970-74 (Box 124, Folder 28)
      - 1975 (Box 124)
    - 1955-69 (Box 124, Folder 29)
  - Parke, Davis and Company
    - 1957-74 (Box 124, Folder 30)
    - 1975 (Box 124)
  - Pe, Misc. 1963-69 (Box 124, Folder 31)
  - Pharmaceutical Manufacturers Association 1959-68 (Box 124, Folder 32)
  - Phelps C. Stowe, Mrs. and Mr. 1955-68 (Box 124, Folder 33)
  - Phelps-Heiner Pamphlet 1959 (Box 124, Folder 34)
  - Pi, Misc. 1967-68 (Box 124, Folder 35)